Front-end Developer

Aaron Mindes

https://aaronmindes.github.io/portfolio/



mindesaaron@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/aaron-mindes-49670617b/

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Angular React
- React Native
- HTML CSS Sass
- MongoDB SQL
- Node.js Nest.js
- Express
- UI/UX Design
- Jira Git Git Kraken
- Java − C − C++
- Android
- Agile Methodologies
- Integration of REST Api

LANGUAGES

- Hebrew | Native
- English | Professional
- French | Native

Highly talented and experienced Front-end developer with a particular penchant for web applications. I acquired a unique blend of technical expertise and creative ingenuity. I ability to grasp new concepts quickly allows me to adapt to different technologies and tools with ease.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Israel Air Force. | Aug 2020 - Nov 2023 |

- Web Platform for Investigation and Research -

As a Full Stack developer, I played a central role in creating an innovative web platform tailored for investigation and research, embedding live video streams and drone telemetry data.

Designed and developed platform features from scratch to meet specific investigation needs.

Proven ability to excel as a designer, optimizing user experience and delivering visually appealing interfaces.

Leveraged Angular, Node.js, Nest.js, JS, TypeScript, Express and MongoDB skills to establish a robust tech ecosystem.

Implemented Agile methodology for efficient, rapid, and adaptive development while using architecture of microservices.

Experienced in efficient data transfer protocols and technologies for real-time data processing for live insights and data archiving for future reference (Wowza, hls, Kafka).

Close collaboration with cross-functional teams to align with goals and ensure client satisfaction.

Played a crucial role in project planning, feature development and deployment, ensuring smooth execution within project deadlines.

Android Developer

ToGo+. |2019 – 2020|

Developed a coaching app while working with a team of designers and artists to ensure captivating visuals and animations.

EDUCATION

PRACTICAL PROGRAMMER ENGINEER 2/2

Ariel University. Ariel | 2022 – 2023 |

PRACTICAL PROGRAMMER ENGINEER 1/2

Ort Singalovski. Tel Aviv | 2021 – 2022 |

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING 2/4

Azrieli College of Engineering. Jerusalem | 2018 – 2020 |